[{"answer": "Well, clearly you help the vice president to help you get votes to get elected.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "How do you see this battleground now?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "If tax cuts create jobs, what went wrong under President Bush?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "Well, yes, ideologically, you would.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 147, "question": "Why wouldn't you ideologically want to do that?", "qSentId": 146}, {"answer": "OVITZ: Well, it's more of the way -- yes, I don't agree when he says you're not paying your fair share.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "You don't agree with that?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "Doesn't it depend as much on the individual businesses?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "Who you going to vote for?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "I think that it's that whole thing, one step forward, one step back.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "-- than it has been, 20 years ago, in your experience, since you began making movies?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "I said people thought he was Jesus.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "What did you say?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "I agree with you.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "How could that not be?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "The bottom line is economics.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "Where do you think if he gets re-elected he should push harder?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "Say it again.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "Did you like the Olympics?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "Did you like the Olympics?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "You don't see I'm wearing my jacket?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "You guys did great.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "Wasn't bad, was it?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "Well, I like to say, first of all, African-Americans alone did not elect President Obama.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "But has it made America more or less racist?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "It was down in Texas I think.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "Where?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "Well, this is the point I make.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "How many people die of gunshots in England every year?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "It averages about 30-odd.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "Two, three?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "They got the -- the Vulcan death grip.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "Well what do you do about NRA, which holds this incredible power?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "I think they both should.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "Should -- should Barack Obama, rather than just talk in this kind of slightly rhetoric way, as he does about guns, should he now push?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "I wanted -- I wanted to hire his speech writer, quite frankly.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "It was an amazing moment, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "I actually feel totally responsible for where he's at.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "Is that what you want to see?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "It scares me, quite frankly.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "Are you nervous?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "More than that actually.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "Like 30 years?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "I -- my hope would be that it actually -- that society is so receptive to the idea that it doesn't make a point, you know.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "Is there a point to it that could really resonate?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "Difficult.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 620, "question": "For you as a central player in this, someone that had known Whitney nearly 30 years, singing at the funeral and so on, what was it like for you?", "qSentId": 619}, {"answer": "Very important two specific reasons.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 628, "question": "What was your motivation for this?", "qSentId": 627}, {"answer": "That she was this difficult diva who lived life in a drug coma, and that, you know, her life at every minute was turmoil.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 634, "question": "What were the biggest misconceptions about her, do you think?", "qSentId": 633}, {"answer": "Probably.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 641, "question": "People like yourself and the family members who weren't exposed to that kind of things, and other friends perhaps some of them not the most desirable?", "qSentId": 640}, {"answer": "I agree that that he wasn't the blame.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 652, "question": "Would you agree with that?", "qSentId": 651}, {"answer": "To a certain degree, because of just being in the same industry.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 659, "question": "Well, it was almost fire and fire, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 658}, {"answer": "No regrets at all.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 665, "question": "Did you ever feel you could have done something to perhaps avert what happened?", "qSentId": 664}, {"answer": "Because I want to remind through these songs that before any association with any party, we all are Americans.", "docId": "120817pmt", "aSentId": 688, "question": "Why such a patriotic album?", "qSentId": 687}]